{
  "Actor": {
    "types": ["character", "nameless", "named", "supernatural", "safeHouse"],
    "templates": {
      "base": {
        "notes": ""
      },
      "npcBase": {
        "stress": {
          "min": 0,
          "value": [0],
          "max": 4,
          "states": [false, false, false, false]
        },
        "skills": "",
        "glance": "",
        "motivation": "",
        "personalityTraits": "",
        "type": ""
      }
    },
    "character": {
      "templates": ["base"],
      "intel": {
        "min": 0,
        "max": 6,
        "value": [0],
        "states": [false, false, false, false, false, false]
      },
      "stress": {
        "min": 0,
        "max": 6,
        "value": [1],
        "states": [true, false, false, false, false, false],
        "manifestTwo": "",
        "manifestThree": "",
        "manifestFour": "",
        "manifestFive": ""
      },
      "load": {
        "light": false,
        "medium": false,
        "heavy": false
      },
      "gear": {
        "light": {
          "one": false,
          "two": false,
          "three": false
        },
        "medium": {
          "one": false,
          "two": false
        },
        "heavy": {
          "one": false
        }
      },
      "expertise": {
        "workedFor": {
          "index": 0,
          "answer": "",
          "options": [
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedFor.placeholder",
              "answer": "-"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedFor.option.1",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedForExpertise.option.1"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedFor.option.2",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedForExpertise.option.2"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedFor.option.3",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedForExpertise.option.3"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedFor.option.4",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedForExpertise.option.4"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedFor.option.5",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.workedForExpertise.option.5"
            }
          ]
        },
        "specialism": {
          "used": false,
          "index": 0,
          "answer": "",
          "options": [
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.placeholder",
              "answer": "-"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.option.1",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialismExpertise.option.1"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.option.2",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialismExpertise.option.2"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.option.3",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialismExpertise.option.3"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.option.4",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialismExpertise.option.4"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.option.5",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialismExpertise.option.5"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.option.6",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialismExpertise.option.6"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.option.7",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialismExpertise.option.7"
            },
            {
              "question": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialism.option.8",
              "answer": "ATDC.actor.expertise.specialismExpertise.option.8"
            }
          ]
        },
        "final": {
          "index": 0,
          "options": [
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.placeholder",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.1",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.2",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.3",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.4",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.5",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.6",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.7",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.8",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.9",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.10",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.11",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.12",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.13",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.14",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.15",
            "ATDC.actor.expertise.final.option.16"
          ]
        },
        "expertiseUsed": false
      },
      "selfDescription": "",
      "nationOrganization": "",
      "whyConfrontConspiracy": {
        "index": 0,
        "text": "",
        "answer": "-",
        "question": "-",
        "options": [
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.placeholder",
            "answerMore": "-",
            "question": "-"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.option.1",
            "answerMore": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.moreAnswer.option.1",
            "question": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.question.option.1"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.option.2",
            "answerMore": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.moreAnswer.option.2",
            "question": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.question.option.2"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.option.3",
            "answerMore": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.moreAnswer.option.3",
            "question": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.question.option.3"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.option.4",
            "answerMore": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.moreAnswer.option.4",
            "question": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.question.option.4"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.option.5",
            "answerMore": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.moreAnswer.option.5",
            "question": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.question.option.5"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.option.6",
            "answerMore": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.moreAnswer.option.6",
            "question": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.question.option.6"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.option.7",
            "answerMore": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.moreAnswer.option.7",
            "question": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.question.option.7"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.answer.option.8",
            "answerMore": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.moreAnswer.option.8",
            "question": "ATDC.actor.biography.whyConfrontConspiracy.question.option.8"
          }
        ]
      },
      "anchor": {
        "name": "",
        "relationship": "",
        "target": false,
        "missing": false,
        "taken": false,
        "details": ""
      },
      "team": {
        "careMostName": "",
        "careMostDetails": "",
        "careLeastName": "",
        "careLeastDetails": ""
      }
    },
    "nameless": {
      "templates": ["base", "npcBase"]
    },
    "named": {
      "templates": ["base", "npcBase"],
      "power": "",
      "powerDetails": "",
      "weaknesses": {
        "compulsion": "",
        "compulsionDetails": "",
        "deterrent": "",
        "deterrentDetails": ""
      }
    },
    "supernatural": {
      "templates": ["base", "npcBase"],
      "power": "",
      "powerDetails": "",
      "weaknesses": {
        "compulsion": "",
        "compulsionDetails": "",
        "deterrent": "",
        "deterrentDetails": ""
      },
      "vulnerability": "",
      "vulnerabilityDetail": ""
    },
    "safeHouse": {
      "templates": ["base"],
      "status": {
        "target": false,
        "blown": false
      },
      "questions": {
        "placeLike": "",
        "reassures": "",
        "vulnerable": "",
        "notIdeal": ""
      },
      "gearBenefit": {
        "heavyWeapons": false,
        "autoWeapons": false,
        "techExplosives": false
      }
    }
  },
  "Item": {
    "types": ["gear", "contact"],
    "templates": {
      "base": {
        "description": ""
      }
    },
    "gear": {
      "templates": ["base"],
      "tags": "",
      "load": 0
    },
    "contact": {
      "templates": ["base"],
      "blown": false,
      "expertise": {
        "index": 0,
        "options": [
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.placeholder",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.1",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.2",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.3",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.4",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.5",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.6",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.7",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.8",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.9",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.10",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.11",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.12",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.13",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.14",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.15",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.16",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.17",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.18",
          "ATDC.actor.relationships.contacts.expertiseOptions.option.19"
        ]
      }
    }
  }
}
